mocospace.com 2012-05-08

# MocoSpace | Política de privacidad

## Privacy Policy

---|---  
  
JNJ Mobile, Inc. dba MocoSpace is a mobile and online social networking service. To enrich our users' experience, we display personal information to other members and visitors, which allows our users to identify each other. MocoSpace members can change their profile information at any time and can control how other members and the service communicates with them. 

MocoSpace cares about online privacy while using our site www.mocospace.com and our MocoSpace mobile applications. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please email us at support@mocospace.com. 

Mocospace has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and these practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at support@mocospace.com. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). The TRUSTe certification covers www.mocospace.com and our MocoSpace mobile applications. 

**Information Collected and Used by MocoSpace**

MocoSpace collects user submitted information such as name, email address, billing address and credit card information or mobile phone number to authenticate users, allow users to pay by phone, pay by credit card or pay pal to purchase virtual currency, and to send notifications and newsletters to those users relating to the MocoSpace service. MocoSpace may also collect user-submitted profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other. 

Our mobile application automatically collects the phones app version and operating system version so that we or our third parties are better able to serve you ads that may be of interest to you and so that we are able to troubleshoot when the app is not responding and where an error occurred. MocoSpace also requests location based information from your mobile device in order to customize your experience and the advertising that you see while on the site. 

MocoSpace may also collect non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the Website, track usage and improve the Website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. 

Member-submitted profile information including pictures may be displayed in order to facilitate user interaction in the MocoSpace social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join MocoSpace, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network. Users within a personal network communicate on MocoSpace with each other through the MocoSpace service, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, MocoSpace may allow users to search for other members using age, gender, first and last name, and location. 

We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by changing their "notification" setting in the user profile. 

From time to time, MocoSpace or a partner may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on MocoSpace. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We use this information to notify winners and deliver their prizes to them. 

We use may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users personally identifiable information for any other purpose. In some instances we may need to share your personal information with third parties in order to complete the sweepstake or contest, if we do so you will be able to make an informed decision as to whether or not you wish to have your personal information shared with these third parties. 

**Invitations and Other Communications to Non-members**

MocoSpace members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails or SMS messages. We will collect your friends e-mail address or phone number only. MocoSpace does not sell these email addresses or phone numbers or use them to send any other communication besides invitations. Recipients of invitations from MocoSpace may contact MocoSpace to request the removal of their information from our database at support@mocospace.com 

**Use of Cookies**

MocoSpace uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from MocoSpace in order to use most functions on the site. Please note that MocoSpace may allow 3rd party advertisers to set and access their own cookies. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the MocoSpace Privacy Policy. We do not have access or control over third party cookies. 

**Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**

We employ or our third party advertising partner or tracking utility company employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a users computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers personally identifiable information. 

**Links**

MocoSpace contains links to other sites. MocoSpace is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on MocoSpace. 

**Chat Rooms and other Public Forums**

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them including photos that you may upload. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at support@mocospace.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

**Import Contacts**

We utilize an import contacts feature to help you keep in touch with your contacts and/ or other members. We make it easy for you to invite people from your address books to join you on our Site. At your request we will search your address book to help you import your contacts to our site. You will then have an opportunity to add any users as a friend if they are already on MocoSpace or to send them an invitation to join MocoSpace if they are not already members. You can select which of your contacts you allow MocoSpace to contact with checkboxes. All boxes are checked initially but you can deselect any or all of the contacts in your list. Any contacts you select will be sent an invitation that originates from MocoSpace but informs the contact that you were the member who initiated the invitation. If the contact does not respond to the invitation, a single follow-up reminder will be sent 7 days after the initial invitation. The purpose of the invitation is to allow your contacts to join MocoSpace. It is also possible to send an invitation by entering a contacts phone number. When a phone number is entered, the contact is sent an SMS message that is marked as from MocoSpace via your user name. The contact is asked to join MocoSpace. 

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name, email address, photos, posts to your wall, and profile information to pre-populate our sign up form and allow you to post photos to your MocoSpace profile. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network. 

**Email Choice/Opt-out**

Members who no longer wish to receive updates, newsletters, or notifications may choose not to by editing their preferences within their settings in the notifications tab. All notification emails and MocoSpace newsletters also include the above instructions for opting-out of those communications in the future. 

**Correcting/Updating or Removing Information**

MocoSpace users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and editing their profile or by emailing us at support@mocospace.com. Furthermore, MocoSpace may remove information from member accounts and postings that violates the MocoSpace Terms of Service. 

We will retain your information (including geo-location data) for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at support@mocospace.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

To request deletion of your profile or an unauthorized profile created about you please contact us at support@mocospace.com. If you are a member already and wish to have you profile deleted you may also login to your account and go to your settings to cancel your membership. 

**Controlling your Privacy**

On the MocoSpace web site, click "Settings" under the "My Home" menu in the top navigation. From there, click the "Privacy Settings" tab to alter your privacy settings. On the MocoSpace mobile site and apps, click the "Menu" button at the top right and select "Settings," then "Privacy Settings" to alter your privacy settings. 

**Third Party Targeted Advertising**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. 

**Security**

MocoSpace member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. MocoSpace takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time For any additional information about the security measures we use on MocoSpace, please contact us at support@mocospace.com. 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security 

When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number and/or geo-location data) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information MocoSpace Collects**

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, MocoSpace will not share, sell, rent or trade your personal information with any third party for their own promotional purposes. Instances where we believe that sharing of your information is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by MocoSpace, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the MocoSpace Terms of Service Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. 

MocoSpace reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of MocoSpace or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. You will be notified via email or prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

**Agents/Service Providers**

We use other third parties such as a credit card processing company to bill you for virtual currency, a targeted advertising company to provide more relevant advertising, and an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf. We may share your name, email address and credit card information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

**Contacting the Website**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, please contact us at: support@mocospace.com, write to JNJ Mobile Inc., 186 South Street, Boston MA 02111, or call 1-877-323-4815. 

_This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 19, 2010_ and was updated on July 15, 2011
